Association of Canadian Publishers fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Literary Press Group, 1975 - 1982; F-57-10; 89 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records of the Literary Press Group. Projects documented are the 'Access Project', or annual LPG catalogue, and the Cloudland Direct Marketing initiative. Included are the constitution, minutes and papers of general and executive meetings, correspondence and memoranda, budgets, grant applications, catalogue supplements, mailing lists, contracts, reports and surveys.
  - Founding, Constitution, Applications, 1975; F-57-10-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-84)
  - Chronological Correspondence and Minutes, 1975 - 1976; F-57-10-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-84)
  - Chronological Correspondence and Minutes, 1976; F-57-10-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-84)
  - General Management Committee - Agenda and Minutes, 1976; F-57-10-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-84)
  - Correspondence, 1975 - 1976; F-57-10-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-84)
  - Catalogue Supplements, 1976; F-57-10-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-84)
  - Catalogue Cost / Benefit Analysis, 1976; F-57-10-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-84)
  - Marketing Survey and Seminar, 1976; F-57-10-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-84)
  - Accounting Seminar, 1976 - 1977; F-57-10-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-84)
  - General Meetings - Agenda, Minutes and Papers, 1977; F-57-10-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-85)
  - Management and Executive Committees - Agenda, Minutes, Papers and Correspondence, 1977; F-57-10-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-85)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1977; F-57-10-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-85)
  - Correspondence, 1976 - 1977; F-57-10-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-85)
  - Access Project / LP6 Budgets - Grant Applications, 1975 - 1977; F-57-10-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-85)
  - Canada Council - Surveys, 1977; F-57-10-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-85)
  - Catalogue Correspondence, 1977; F-57-10-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-85)
  - Catalogue Cost / Benefit Analysis, 1977; F-57-10-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-85)
  - Catalogue - Users Survey, 1977; F-57-10-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-85)
  - History of LPG, 1977; F-57-10-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-85)
  - Membership - Applications and Correspondence, 1976 - 1977; F-57-10-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-86)
  - Minutes - Annual Meeting, 1978; F-57-10-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-86)
  - Minutes - Executive Meetings, 1978; F-57-10-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-86)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - Edmonton Regional Meeting and Production Seminar, 1978; F-57-10-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-86)
  - Minutes and Correspondence - St. John's Regional Meeting, 1978; F-57-10-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-86)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1978; F-57-10-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-86)
  - Correspondence, 1978; F-57-10-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-86)
  - Advertising, 1977 - 1979; F-57-10-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-86)
  - Book Orders Received, 1977 - 1978; F-57-10-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-86)
  - Catalogue Spring '78 Correspondence, 1978; F-57-10-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-86)
  - Catalogue Fall '78 Correspondence, 1978; F-57-10-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-86)
  - Grant Applications, 1977 - 1978; F-57-10-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-87)
  - Central Ontario Regional Library System Conference, 1978; F-57-10-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-87)
  - Mailing Lists and Distribution, 1978; F-57-10-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-87)
  - Members - memoranda to, 1978; F-57-10-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 57-87)
  - Translators, 1977 - 1979; F-57-10-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 57-87)
  - Agendas, Minutes and Papers - Executive Regional Meetings, 1979; F-57-10-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 57-87)
  - Agendas, Minutes and Papers - Executive, 1979; F-57-10-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 57-87)
  - Agendas, Minutes and Papers - Executive Annual General Meetings, 1979; F-57-10-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 57-87)
  - Agendas and Correspondence - Regional Meetings Regina and Victoria, 1978 - 1979; F-57-10-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 57-87)
  - Correspondence, 1979; F-57-10-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 57-87)
  - Budget, 1979; F-57-10-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 57-87)
  - Canada Council - Correspondence, 1979; F-57-10-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 57-87)
  - Catalogue Correspondence, 1979; F-57-10-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 57-87)
  - Committee of Small Magazine Editors and Publishers (COSMEP), 1978 - 1979; F-57-10-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 57-88)
  - Displays and Distribution possibilities, 1978 - 1979; F-57-10-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 57-88)
  - Distribution in England, 1978 - 1979; F-57-10-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 57-88)
  - Distribution Possibilities, 1979; F-57-10-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 57-88)
  - Members - memoranda to, 1979; F-57-10-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 57-88)
  - Membership Applications, 1979; F-57-10-0-0-49 (Archival box - standard 57-88)
  - Trade Fairs - CBA, ABA, 1979; F-57-10-0-0-50 (Archival box - standard 57-88)
  - Minutes - Executive and Regional Meetings, 1980; F-57-10-0-0-51 (Archival box - standard 57-88)
  - Agenda and Papers - Annual and Special General Meetings, 1980; F-57-10-0-0-52 (Archival box - standard 57-88)
  - Agenda and Papers - Regional Meeting, Montreal, 1980; F-57-10-0-0-53 (Archival box - standard 57-88)
  - Correpondence, 1980; F-57-10-0-0-54 (Archival box - standard 57-88)
  - Budget, 1979 - 1980; F-57-10-0-0-55 (Archival box - standard 57-88)
  - Canada Council, 1980; F-57-10-0-0-56 (Archival box - standard 57-88)
  - Catalogue Correspondence, 1980; F-57-10-0-0-57 (Archival box - standard 57-89)
  - Membership - memoranda to, 1980; F-57-10-0-0-58 (Archival box - standard 57-89)
  - Ontario Arts Council, 1980; F-57-10-0-0-59 (Archival box - standard 57-89)
  - Agendas, Minutes and Papers - Executive Annual General Meetings, 1981; F-57-10-0-0-60 (Archival box - standard 57-89)
  - Correspondence, 1981 - 1982; F-57-10-0-0-61 (Archival box - standard 57-89)
  - Catalogue Correspondence, 1981; F-57-10-0-0-62 (Archival box - standard 57-89)
  - Clipping Survey, 1981; F-57-10-0-0-63 (Archival box - standard 57-89)
  - Displays, 1981; F-57-10-0-0-64 (Archival box - standard 57-89)
  - Market Research Seminar, 1981; F-57-10-0-0-65 (Archival box - standard 57-89)
  - Quill and Quire, 1981; F-57-10-0-0-66 (Archival box - standard 57-89)
  - Bookstore Survey, F-57-10-0-0-67 (Archival box - standard 57-89)
  - Cloudland - Correspondence, 1978 - 1980; F-57-10-0-0-68 (Archival box - standard 57-89)
  - Cloudland - Advertising, 1979 - 1980; F-57-10-0-0-69 (Archival box - standard 57-89)
  - Cloudland - Budget, 1979 - 1981; F-57-10-0-0-70 (Archival box - standard 57-89)
  - Cloudland - Contracts, 1979 - 1980; F-57-10-0-0-71 (Archival box - standard 57-90)
  - Cloudland - Correspondence, 1980; F-57-10-0-0-72 (Archival box - standard 57-90)
  - Cloudland - Correspondence to members, 1979 - 1980; F-57-10-0-0-73 (Archival box - standard 57-90)
  - Cloudland - Mailing Lists, 1979; F-57-10-0-0-74 (Archival box - standard 57-90)
  - Cloudland - Mailing Lists, Bookstores, 1979 - 1980; F-57-10-0-0-75 (Archival box - standard 57-90)
  - Cloudland - Marketing, 1979; F-57-10-0-0-76 (Archival box - standard 57-90)
  - Cloudland - Reports, 1979 - 1981; F-57-10-0-0-77 (Archival box - standard 57-90)
  - Cloudland - Warehouse Manager Correspondence, 1979 - 1981; F-57-10-0-0-78 (Archival box - standard 57-90)
  - Cloudland - Warehouse Manager order lists, 1979 - 1981; F-57-10-0-0-79 (Archival box - standard 57-90)
- Book Purchase Program, 1972 - 1983; F-57-11; 25 cm of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the creation, operation and administration of the Book Purchase Program. The records document IPA involvement in its planning and administration, as well as program details such as titles and recipients selected. Included are minutes, speech, clippings, press releases, correspondence, address and account book, budgets, lists and purchase orders.
  - General Correspondence, 1972 - 1973; F-57-11-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-91)
  - Purchase Orders - Round 1, 1972; F-57-11-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-91)
  - General Correspondence - Round 2, 1973; F-57-11-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-91)
  - Purchase Orders - Round 2, 1973; F-57-11-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-91)
  - General Correspondence, 1973 - 1974; F-57-11-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-91)
  - Budget, 1973 - 1974; F-57-11-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-91)
  - Procedures - Application, shipping, 1973 - 1974; F-57-11-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-91)
  - Reports, 1973 - 1974; F-57-11-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-91)
  - Title lists, book kit lists, 1973 - 1974; F-57-11-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-91)
  - Recipients' Letters of Acknowledgment, 1974; F-57-11-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-91)
  - General Correspondence, 1974 - 1975; F-57-11-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-91)
  - Budget, 1974 - 1975; F-57-11-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-91)
  - Title lists - purchase orders, 1974 - 1975; F-57-11-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-91)
  - Recipients' Letters of Acknowledgment, 1974 - 1975; F-57-11-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-91)
  - Kit list - purchase orders, 1975 - 1976; F-57-11-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-91)
  - Recipients' Letters of Acknowledgment, 1975; F-57-11-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - Recipients' Letters of Acknowledgment, 1976; F-57-11-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - Canada Council Correspondence, 1976 - 1977; F-57-11-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - Purchase Orders, 1976 - 1977; F-57-11-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - Reports, 1976 - 1977; F-57-11-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - Recipients' Lists, 1977; F-57-11-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - Canada Council Correspondence, 1977 - 1978; F-57-11-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - List of Titles - Purchase Orders, 1977 - 1978; F-57-11-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - Recipients' List, 1977 - 1978; F-57-11-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - Reports, 1977 - 1978; F-57-11-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - Canada Council Correspondence, 1978 - 1979; F-57-11-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - Purchase Order - Title Lists, 1978; F-57-11-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - Reports and Budget, 1978 - 1979; F-57-11-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - Recipients' Letters of Acknowledgment, 1979; F-57-11-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - Title List - Reports and Correspondence, 1979 - 1980; F-57-11-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - Title List - Reports and Correspondence, 1980 - 1981; F-57-11-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - Title List - Correspondence, Recipients, 1981 - 1982; F-57-11-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
  - Title List - Reports, 1982 - 1983; F-57-11-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-92)
- Projects, 1974 - 1980; F-57-12; 1.01 m of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the operation of three projects initiated by the IPA: Canadabooks, Canadian Basic Books and Canadian Book Information Centre. The records of the overseeing body, Canadian Publishers Project Co-ordinating Committee, are absent. Included are correspondence, legal documents, minutes, notes, catalogues, questionnaires, audit statements, budgets and reports.
  - Canadabooks, 1974 - 1980; F-57-12-1; 80 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of records relating to the Canadabooks project. Documented are its endeavors to increase the sale of members' titles in the educational field through salespersons and production of joint catalogues. Included are bylaws, minutes and papers of the Board of Governors and general meetings, correspondence, financial statements, contracts, reports and catalogues.
    - Legal Documents and Correspondence - Incorporation Founding By-Laws, 1974 - 1975; F-57-12-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-93)
    - Board of Directors - Minutes, Legal Documents, 1976 - 1977; F-57-12-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-93)
    - Board of Directors - Minutes, Legal Documents, 1977 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-93)
    - Legal Documents, 1978; F-57-12-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-93)
    - Annual General Meetings Minutes, 1977 - 1979; F-57-12-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-93)
    - Correspondence and Papers (ACP) 1/2, 1976 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-93)
    - Correspondence and Papers (ACP) 2/2, 1976 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-93)
    - Handbook, 1977; F-57-12-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-93)
    - Canadabooks - Neil McBurney, B.C. Division, 1975 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-93)
    - Ester McNeil, Displays Montreal, 1975 - 1977; F-57-12-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-94)
    - Jim Patchell, Western Representative, 1975 - 1976; F-57-12-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-94)
    - Correspondence and Working Notes - Diane Davey, Manager, 1977 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-94)
    - Legal Correspondence, 1976 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-94)
    - Catalogue General, 1978; F-57-12-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-94)
    - Catalogue Participation Forms, 1978; F-57-12-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-94)
    - Catalogue Participation Forms - Withdrawals, 1978; F-57-12-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-94)
    - Catalogue Participation Telephone Campaign, 1978; F-57-12-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-94)
    - Correspondence with Publishers, 1978; F-57-12-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-94)
    - Catalogue Mailing Lists, 1978; F-57-12-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-94)
    - Catalogue Production and Mailing, 1978; F-57-12-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-94)
    - Catalogue Revenue Calculations, 1978; F-57-12-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-94)
    - Catalogue Correspondence, 1978 - 1979; F-57-12-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-94)
    - Catalogue Questionnaire, 1979 - 1980; F-57-12-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-94)
    - Orders and Order Inquiries, 1978; F-57-12-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-94)
    - Curriculum Fund - NC Press, 1977 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-95)
    - Financial Records - Audited Statements, 1975 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-95)
    - Financial Records - Budgets and Balance Sheets, 1974 - 1976; F-57-12-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-95)
    - Financial Records - Budgets and Balance Sheets, 1976 - 1979; F-57-12-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-95)
    - Ontario Arts Council - Applications, 1977 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-95)
    - Sales Reports, 1975 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-95)
    - Provincial Sales Reports, 1975 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-95)
    - Statements of Commissions, 1976 - 1977; F-57-12-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-95)
    - Statements of Commissions, 1977 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-95)
    - Outstanding Commissions, 1978; F-57-12-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 57-95)
    - Member File - Before We are Six, 1976 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 57-95)
    - Member File - Belford Book Distributing, 1975 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 57-96)
    - Member File - Black Rose Books, 1974 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 57-96)
    - Member File - Canadian Council of Teachers of English, 1975 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 57-96)
    - Member File - Dalzell Books and Cover Press, 1974 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 57-96)
    - Member File - Dundurn Press, 1975 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 57-96)
    - Member File - Filmstrip and Slide Lab., 1976 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 57-96)
    - Member File - Greey de Pencier Publications, 1976 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 57-96)
    - Member File - Institute of Social and Economic Research, 1976 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 57-96)
    - Member File - James Lorimer and Co., 1974 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 57-96)
    - Member File - Kids Can Press, 1976 - 1977; F-57-12-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 57-97)
    - Member File - Learnxs Press, 1976 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 57-97)
    - Member File - N.C. Multimedia, 1977 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 57-97)
    - Member File - N.C. Press Ltd., 1975 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-48 (Archival box - standard 57-97)
    - Member File - New Hogtown Press, 1977 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-49 (Archival box - standard 57-97)
    - Member File - New Star Books, 1974 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-50 (Archival box - standard 57-97)
    - Member File - Peter Martin Associates, 1974 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-51 (Archival box - standard 57-97)
    - Member File - Potlatch Publications, 1975 - 1977; F-57-12-1-0-52 (Archival box - standard 57-97)
    - Member File - Press Gang Publishers, 1976; F-57-12-1-0-53 (Archival box - standard 57-97)
    - Member File - Queenston House, 1976 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-54 (Archival box - standard 57-97)
    - Member File - Steel Rail Publishing, 1976 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-55 (Archival box - standard 57-97)
    - Member File - Talon Books Correspondence, 1974 - 1977; F-57-12-1-0-56 (Archival box - standard 57-97)
    - Member File - Talon Books Correspondence and Sales Reports, 1974 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-57 (Archival box - standard 57-97)
    - Member File - Tree Frog Press, 1976 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-58 (Archival box - standard 57-98)
    - Member File - U. of Alberta Press, 1976 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-59 (Archival box - standard 57-98)
    - Member File - U.B.C. Press, 1974 - 1976; F-57-12-1-0-60 (Archival box - standard 57-98)
    - Member File - U.B.C. Press, 1977 - 1979; F-57-12-1-0-61 (Archival box - standard 57-98)
    - Member File - Western Education Development, 1976 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-62 (Archival box - standard 57-98)
    - Member File - Western Geographical Series, 1976 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-63 (Archival box - standard 57-98)
    - Member File - Women's Educational Press, 1975 - 1977; F-57-12-1-0-64 (Archival box - standard 57-98)
    - Member File - Yorkminster Publishing, 1975 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-65 (Archival box - standard 57-98)
    - Catalogues and Flyers, 1975 - 1976; F-57-12-1-0-66 (Archival box - standard 57-98)
    - Catalogues, 1976 - 1977; F-57-12-1-0-67 (Archival box - standard 57-98)
    - Catalogues, 1977 - 1978; F-57-12-1-0-68 (Archival box - standard 57-99)
    - Catalogues, 1978 - 1979; F-57-12-1-0-69 (Archival box - standard 57-99)
  - Canadian Basic Books, 1975 - 1977; F-57-12-2; 4 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of records relating to the Canadian Basic Books project. Included are limited amount of correspondence, the catalogues and final report of the project.
    - Correspondence and Final Report, 1975 - 1977; F-57-12-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-99)
    - Catalogues, 1975 - 1976; F-57-12-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-99)
  - Canadian Book Information Centre, 1975 - 1976; F-57-12-3; 17 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of records of the Canadian Book Information Centre prior to its restructuring in 1976. Also documented is the Library Information Project, a survey of libraries intended to enhance the services offered by publishers and suppliers. Included are minutes and papers of the management and executive committees, correspondence, brochures, catalogues, reports and budgets.
    - Management Committee - Agenda, Minutes and Papers, 1975; F-57-12-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-99)
    - Management Committee - Agenda, Minutes and Papers 1/3, 1976; F-57-12-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-99)
    - Management Committee - Agenda, Minutes and Papers 2/3, 1976; F-57-12-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-100)
    - Management Committee - Agenda, Minutes and Papers 3/3, 1976; F-57-12-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-100)
    - Background - pamphlets, reports, bulletins, 1975 - 1976; F-57-12-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-100)
    - Budget and Funding correspondence, 1976; F-57-12-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-100)
    - ACP - Memoranda, correspondence: Rosemary Duff, 1976; F-57-12-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-100)
    - Display Program, 1976; F-57-12-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-100)
    - History of Publishing, 1975; F-57-12-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-100)
    - Library Infromation Project Survey, 1976; F-57-12-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-100)
    - Library Infromation Project Reports, 1976; F-57-12-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-100)
    - Selection Tools - correspondence, 1976; F-57-12-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-100)
- Grant applications and financial statements, 1972 - 1982; F-57-13; 13 cm of textual records
  Series consists of grant applications to the Canada Council and Ontario Arts Council by the ACP and its affiliates for the years 1979-1981 and 1983, and of ACP audited financial statements for the years 1972, 1974, 1979 and 1981.
  Included are budgets, financial statements, annual and semi-annual reports, correspondence and proposals for the ACP, the BC, Alberta and Atlantic publishers, the LPG and the projects Canadabooks and Canadian Book Information Centre projects. The files have been maintained in their original alphabetized order.
  Miscellaneous audited IPA/ACP Financial Statements are also found in the series.
  - Association of Book Publishers of B.C., 1978; F-57-13-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Association of Book Publishers of B.C., 1979 - 1980; F-57-13-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Association of Book Publishers of B.C., 1980 - 1981; F-57-13-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Association of Canadian Publishers, 1978 - 1979; F-57-13-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Association of Canadian Publishers, 1979 - 1980; F-57-13-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Association of Canadian Publishers, 1980 - 1981; F-57-13-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Alberta Publishers Association, 1978; F-57-13-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Atlantic Publishers Association, 1978 - 1979; F-57-13-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Atlantic Publishers Association, 1979 - 1980; F-57-13-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Atlantic Publishers Association, 1980 - 1981; F-57-13-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Canadabooks Grant, 1979; F-57-13-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Canadian Book Information Centre, 1978 - 1980; F-57-13-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Catalogue Budget - Prairie, 1981; F-57-13-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Literary Press Group, 1978 - 1980; F-57-13-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Grants - Ontario Arts Council, Canada Council, 1977 - 1978; F-57-13-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Grants, 1978 - 1979; F-57-13-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Grants, 1979 - 1980; F-57-13-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Canada Council Grants, 1980 - 1981; F-57-13-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Ministry of Culture and Recreation, 1980 - 1981; F-57-13-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Canada Council Applications, 1979 - 1982; F-57-13-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
  - Financial Statemets, 1972 - 1981; F-57-13-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-101)
- Book and Periodical Development Council, 1975 - 1981; F-57-14; 25 cm of textual records